<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<source>
  <publisher>
    <name>Zonos</name>
  </publisher>
  <publisherurl>https://zonos.com</publisherurl>
  <lastBuildDate>2026-05-05</lastBuildDate>
  <job>
    <title>Corporate Broker (Licensed Customs Broker)St.George UTFull-time</title>
    <date>2026-05-05</date>
    <referencenumber>77430071</referencenumber>
    <url>https://jobs.deel.com/zonos/job-details/815a46a0-a70f-4842-8ffe-b4c6f8e07802/overview</url>
    <company>Zonos</company>
    <city>Remote</city>
    <state/>
    <country>US</country>
    <postalcode/>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;At Zonos we provide scalable technology to simplify the complexities of international commerce, making it accessible to everyone. We create products that allow businesses to take complete control of their cross-border trade experience. Our SaaS solutions alleviate the headaches of cross-border trade with APIs and software that provide businesses with the tools and data they need to scale globally, including the only true landed cost solution on the market. If you're looking to join a company with a strong mission and vision that puts people first, we want to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This position is based in St. George, Utah.Relocation assistance is provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;About the Role&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're looking for a Licensed Customs Broker to establish the compliance framework for a high-growth technology company reshaping how e-commerce and international trade work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently selected for CBP's Commercial Solutions Opening Pilot (CSOP) program and recognized as a CBP Qualified Party for AI-driven trade compliance solutions, Zonos is working directly with CBP on next-generation customs solutions. You'll be building compliant processes at the intersection of cutting-edge technology and regulatory requirements, architecting how compliance works when automation handles the heavy lifting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What You'll Work On&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish and maintain compliant processes for customs business activities within Zonos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide oversight and sign-off on classification guidance, duty calculations, and CBP interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build internal procedures that bridge our technology with regulatory requirements, ensuring Zonos operations meet all customs broker obligations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with modern technology and automated workflows, translating regulatory requirements into practical, scalable operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build compliant systems at scale where millions of shipments depend on getting customs right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Why This Role Is Different&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll be working with a team that's building the future of cross-border commerce, working directly with CBP on innovative pilot programs, and establishing how compliance works when technology does the heavy lifting. This is officer-level work: building systems, making strategic decisions, and representing Zonos's compliance posture to regulators and partners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What We're Looking For&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have an active US Customs Broker License.That's the baseline. But we're looking for more than credentials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone who understands e-commerce customs operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You've dealt with the incomplete data, the misclassifications from sellers who don't understand what they're shipping, and all the chaos of moving goods across borders at scale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You've established compliant processes before. You're comfortable in a fast-paced technology environment where figuring out how regulations apply to new business models takes thought and good judgment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can translate regulatory requirements into systems that work in practice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You think about how processes will scale, where they'll break, and how to build in quality from the start.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You've worked effectively with CBP and understand that compliance is a partnership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required:Active US Customs Broker License3+ years of customs brokerage experienceStrong understanding of PGA requirementsExperience with PGA permits, certifications, and compliance proceduresAbility to work effectively with both CBP and PGA officials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active US Customs Broker License&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of customs brokerage experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of PGA requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PGA permits, certifications, and compliance procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively with both CBP and PGA officials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helpful but not required:Familiarity with ACE/ABI systemsExperience with brokerage software platforms (CargoWise, Descartes, WiseTech, Customs City)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ACE/ABI systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with brokerage software platforms (CargoWise, Descartes, WiseTech, Customs City)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active US Customs Broker License&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of customs brokerage experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of PGA requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PGA permits, certifications, and compliance procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively with both CBP and PGA officials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ACE/ABI systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with brokerage software platforms (CargoWise, Descartes, WiseTech, Customs City)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What We Offer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual salaries will vary based on various factors such as education, experience, training, scope, etc. Salary is just one component of our total compensation package.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision, &amp; Life - we pay 100% of the employee premium!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave and other life event leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k retirement plan with generous company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible time off - we require all our Zonuts to take a minimum of 2 weeks off per year. Take some time to relax!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 month paid time off at 5 year anniversary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office stocked with snacks and drinks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly company lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    <jobtype>Full-time</jobtype>
    <category/>
    <experience/>
    <education/>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>Senior/Staff Backend EngineerSt.George UTFull-time$130,000 USD - $200,000 USD</title>
    <date>2026-05-05</date>
    <referencenumber>19426397</referencenumber>
    <url>https://jobs.deel.com/zonos/job-details/6ede6e6a-1b6a-4eae-828e-640af99ee809/overview</url>
    <company>Zonos</company>
    <city>Remote</city>
    <state/>
    <country>US</country>
    <postalcode/>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Zonos is the AI operating system for cross-border trade, powering everything from checkout to customs clearance for more than 50,000 ecommerce merchants and 70+ postal operators across 200+ countries. We help businesses grow globally by removing the complexity of international commerce—calculating, collecting, and guaranteeing duties, taxes, and fees at checkout so shoppers see the true total cost upfront, eliminating surprise charges at delivery and the burden of managing country-specific tax requirements. Beyond ecommerce, Zonos supports carriers, postal operators, marketplaces, and customs agencies with AI-driven tools that infer and validate key customs data, including HS codes, country of origin, and customs value, alongside licensed customs brokerage services that ensure goods move compliantly and efficiently across borders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're hiring engineers who build things customers actually use. The title says &quot;backend,&quot; but what we want first is a product-minded problem solver who happens to be excellent at backend systems. We’re looking for someone who cares more about whether a feature ships and works than about which framework got them there. The systems we build are real-time, mission-critical, and genuinely complex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our backend runs primarily on Java/JVM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How We're Organized&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We don't have product managers. At the senior and staff level,you talk to customers directly, understand their problems, decide what to build, and ship it.That's not a side responsibility; it's the job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In practice, that means:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritization happens at the initiative level.Engineering is organized into a small number of initiatives, each with a named owner and tech lead who set direction and resolve roadmap conflicts. You're not prioritizing in a vacuum,  but you do own what gets built inside your area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saying no is part of the job.Customers and internal stakeholders will ask for things. Part of being senior here is having the judgment to push back, propose alternatives, or escalate when trade-offs need a wider conversation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You're supported on customer work, not thrown into it.Customer success, sales engineering, and support handle the front line. When you join a customer call, it's because the problem needs an engineer in the room, not because you're running the account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conflicts go to the tech leads and CTO.Disagreements about architecture, scope, or priority don't fester. We resolve them quickly, in writing, with clear owners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've worked in environments where PM hand-offs slowed you down or watered down the product, you'll recognize why we do it this way. If you've never owned the full loop before, this will be a stretch — and that's fine, as long as you're hungry for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Working with Agentic Tools&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agentic development has changed what senior engineering looks like day-to-day. We're not throwing out craft. If anything, the bar on judgment, architecture, and verification has gone up. But the mechanics have shifted: more time spent specifying problems clearly, reviewing generated code with a critical eye, and catching the subtle failure modes that agents miss. Less time on boilerplate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The engineers doing the best work here treat agents the way a strong senior treats a sharp but inexperienced teammate: delegate the right things, verify carefully, and own the outcome. They also understand that LLM intelligence is jagged — brilliant in some places, naive in others — and have built the instincts to know when to trust the output and when to dig deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want engineers who've already adopted these tools, formed real opinions about where they help and where they don't, and can bring that experience to the team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What You'll Do&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with customers to understand problems worth solving — and decide which ones to solve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design backend systems and APIs that scale to billions of transactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use agentic tools effectively to implement features, while holding a high bar on what ships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own architecture and trade-off decisions in your domain (we use a Bronze/Silver/Gold blast-radius framework — you'll learn it fast)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debug production issues across services, including the gnarly ones that require deep system understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Champion reliability, observability, and blast-radius awareness in everything you ship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raise the bar in code review — for both human-written and agent-generated code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor teammates on customer empathy, spec-driven development, and getting real leverage from agents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;You Might Be a Great Fit If You...&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead with product instinct. You ask &quot;should we build this?&quot; before &quot;how do we build this?&quot; — and you're comfortable getting on a call with a customer to find out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want to own the full loop: customer problem → spec → implementation → ship → follow-up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are fluent in Java/JVM — or fluent enough to read, debug, and verify Java code at a senior level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have integrated agentic tools (Claude Code, Cursor, etc.) into your daily workflow and have grounded opinions about what works and what doesn't&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are inquisitive by default — you read papers, try new tools, talk to customers, and bring ideas back to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take ownership. When something breaks, you fix it. When something is unclear, you go find out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have e-commerce, payments, or international trade background — or are excited to go deep in the space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want to live and work in sunny St. George, Utah, with a real work-life balance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we offer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$130,000 to $200,000+ - Actual salaries will vary based on various factors such as education, experience, training, scope, etc. The salary noted is just one component of our total compensation package.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision, &amp; Life - we pay 100% of the employee premium!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave and other life event leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k retirement plan with generous company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible time off - we require all our Zonuts to take a minimum of 2 weeks off per year. Take some time to relax!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 month paid time off at 5 year anniversary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office stocked with snacks and drinks + weekly team lunch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly company lunch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    <jobtype>Full-time</jobtype>
    <category/>
    <experience/>
    <education/>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>Corporate Broker (Licensed Customs Broker)St.George UTFull-time</title>
    <date>2026-05-05</date>
    <referencenumber>77430071</referencenumber>
    <url>https://jobs.deel.com/zonos/job-details/815a46a0-a70f-4842-8ffe-b4c6f8e07802/overview</url>
    <company>Zonos</company>
    <city>Remote</city>
    <state/>
    <country>US</country>
    <postalcode/>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;At Zonos we provide scalable technology to simplify the complexities of international commerce, making it accessible to everyone. We create products that allow businesses to take complete control of their cross-border trade experience. Our SaaS solutions alleviate the headaches of cross-border trade with APIs and software that provide businesses with the tools and data they need to scale globally, including the only true landed cost solution on the market. If you're looking to join a company with a strong mission and vision that puts people first, we want to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This position is based in St. George, Utah.Relocation assistance is provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;About the Role&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're looking for a Licensed Customs Broker to establish the compliance framework for a high-growth technology company reshaping how e-commerce and international trade work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently selected for CBP's Commercial Solutions Opening Pilot (CSOP) program and recognized as a CBP Qualified Party for AI-driven trade compliance solutions, Zonos is working directly with CBP on next-generation customs solutions. You'll be building compliant processes at the intersection of cutting-edge technology and regulatory requirements, architecting how compliance works when automation handles the heavy lifting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What You'll Work On&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish and maintain compliant processes for customs business activities within Zonos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide oversight and sign-off on classification guidance, duty calculations, and CBP interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build internal procedures that bridge our technology with regulatory requirements, ensuring Zonos operations meet all customs broker obligations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with modern technology and automated workflows, translating regulatory requirements into practical, scalable operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build compliant systems at scale where millions of shipments depend on getting customs right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Why This Role Is Different&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll be working with a team that's building the future of cross-border commerce, working directly with CBP on innovative pilot programs, and establishing how compliance works when technology does the heavy lifting. This is officer-level work: building systems, making strategic decisions, and representing Zonos's compliance posture to regulators and partners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What We're Looking For&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have an active US Customs Broker License.That's the baseline. But we're looking for more than credentials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone who understands e-commerce customs operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You've dealt with the incomplete data, the misclassifications from sellers who don't understand what they're shipping, and all the chaos of moving goods across borders at scale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You've established compliant processes before. You're comfortable in a fast-paced technology environment where figuring out how regulations apply to new business models takes thought and good judgment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can translate regulatory requirements into systems that work in practice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You think about how processes will scale, where they'll break, and how to build in quality from the start.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You've worked effectively with CBP and understand that compliance is a partnership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required:Active US Customs Broker License3+ years of customs brokerage experienceStrong understanding of PGA requirementsExperience with PGA permits, certifications, and compliance proceduresAbility to work effectively with both CBP and PGA officials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active US Customs Broker License&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of customs brokerage experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of PGA requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PGA permits, certifications, and compliance procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively with both CBP and PGA officials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helpful but not required:Familiarity with ACE/ABI systemsExperience with brokerage software platforms (CargoWise, Descartes, WiseTech, Customs City)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ACE/ABI systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with brokerage software platforms (CargoWise, Descartes, WiseTech, Customs City)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active US Customs Broker License&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of customs brokerage experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of PGA requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with PGA permits, certifications, and compliance procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively with both CBP and PGA officials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ACE/ABI systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with brokerage software platforms (CargoWise, Descartes, WiseTech, Customs City)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What We Offer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual salaries will vary based on various factors such as education, experience, training, scope, etc. Salary is just one component of our total compensation package.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision, &amp; Life - we pay 100% of the employee premium!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave and other life event leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k retirement plan with generous company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible time off - we require all our Zonuts to take a minimum of 2 weeks off per year. Take some time to relax!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 month paid time off at 5 year anniversary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office stocked with snacks and drinks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly company lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    <jobtype>Full-time</jobtype>
    <category/>
    <experience/>
    <education/>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>Senior/Staff Backend EngineerSt.George UTFull-time$130,000 USD - $200,000 USD</title>
    <date>2026-05-05</date>
    <referencenumber>19426397</referencenumber>
    <url>https://jobs.deel.com/zonos/job-details/6ede6e6a-1b6a-4eae-828e-640af99ee809/overview</url>
    <company>Zonos</company>
    <city>Remote</city>
    <state/>
    <country>US</country>
    <postalcode/>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Zonos is the AI operating system for cross-border trade, powering everything from checkout to customs clearance for more than 50,000 ecommerce merchants and 70+ postal operators across 200+ countries. We help businesses grow globally by removing the complexity of international commerce—calculating, collecting, and guaranteeing duties, taxes, and fees at checkout so shoppers see the true total cost upfront, eliminating surprise charges at delivery and the burden of managing country-specific tax requirements. Beyond ecommerce, Zonos supports carriers, postal operators, marketplaces, and customs agencies with AI-driven tools that infer and validate key customs data, including HS codes, country of origin, and customs value, alongside licensed customs brokerage services that ensure goods move compliantly and efficiently across borders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're hiring engineers who build things customers actually use. The title says &quot;backend,&quot; but what we want first is a product-minded problem solver who happens to be excellent at backend systems. We’re looking for someone who cares more about whether a feature ships and works than about which framework got them there. The systems we build are real-time, mission-critical, and genuinely complex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our backend runs primarily on Java/JVM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How We're Organized&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We don't have product managers. At the senior and staff level,you talk to customers directly, understand their problems, decide what to build, and ship it.That's not a side responsibility; it's the job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In practice, that means:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritization happens at the initiative level.Engineering is organized into a small number of initiatives, each with a named owner and tech lead who set direction and resolve roadmap conflicts. You're not prioritizing in a vacuum,  but you do own what gets built inside your area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saying no is part of the job.Customers and internal stakeholders will ask for things. Part of being senior here is having the judgment to push back, propose alternatives, or escalate when trade-offs need a wider conversation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You're supported on customer work, not thrown into it.Customer success, sales engineering, and support handle the front line. When you join a customer call, it's because the problem needs an engineer in the room, not because you're running the account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conflicts go to the tech leads and CTO.Disagreements about architecture, scope, or priority don't fester. We resolve them quickly, in writing, with clear owners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've worked in environments where PM hand-offs slowed you down or watered down the product, you'll recognize why we do it this way. If you've never owned the full loop before, this will be a stretch — and that's fine, as long as you're hungry for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Working with Agentic Tools&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agentic development has changed what senior engineering looks like day-to-day. We're not throwing out craft. If anything, the bar on judgment, architecture, and verification has gone up. But the mechanics have shifted: more time spent specifying problems clearly, reviewing generated code with a critical eye, and catching the subtle failure modes that agents miss. Less time on boilerplate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The engineers doing the best work here treat agents the way a strong senior treats a sharp but inexperienced teammate: delegate the right things, verify carefully, and own the outcome. They also understand that LLM intelligence is jagged — brilliant in some places, naive in others — and have built the instincts to know when to trust the output and when to dig deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want engineers who've already adopted these tools, formed real opinions about where they help and where they don't, and can bring that experience to the team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What You'll Do&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with customers to understand problems worth solving — and decide which ones to solve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design backend systems and APIs that scale to billions of transactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use agentic tools effectively to implement features, while holding a high bar on what ships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own architecture and trade-off decisions in your domain (we use a Bronze/Silver/Gold blast-radius framework — you'll learn it fast)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debug production issues across services, including the gnarly ones that require deep system understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Champion reliability, observability, and blast-radius awareness in everything you ship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raise the bar in code review — for both human-written and agent-generated code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor teammates on customer empathy, spec-driven development, and getting real leverage from agents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;You Might Be a Great Fit If You...&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead with product instinct. You ask &quot;should we build this?&quot; before &quot;how do we build this?&quot; — and you're comfortable getting on a call with a customer to find out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want to own the full loop: customer problem → spec → implementation → ship → follow-up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are fluent in Java/JVM — or fluent enough to read, debug, and verify Java code at a senior level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have integrated agentic tools (Claude Code, Cursor, etc.) into your daily workflow and have grounded opinions about what works and what doesn't&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are inquisitive by default — you read papers, try new tools, talk to customers, and bring ideas back to the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take ownership. When something breaks, you fix it. When something is unclear, you go find out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have e-commerce, payments, or international trade background — or are excited to go deep in the space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want to live and work in sunny St. George, Utah, with a real work-life balance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we offer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$130,000 to $200,000+ - Actual salaries will vary based on various factors such as education, experience, training, scope, etc. The salary noted is just one component of our total compensation package.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision, &amp; Life - we pay 100% of the employee premium!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave and other life event leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k retirement plan with generous company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible time off - we require all our Zonuts to take a minimum of 2 weeks off per year. Take some time to relax!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 month paid time off at 5 year anniversary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office stocked with snacks and drinks + weekly team lunch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly company lunch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    <jobtype>Full-time</jobtype>
    <category/>
    <experience/>
    <education/>
  </job>
</source>
